https://cgpirates.com/cookie-policy-eu/

Cookie policy (EU) - CGPirates!
CGPirates!
YARR!
Let's learn something fun!
Home
Free Video Learning
The Imperial Knight Lessons – Free and frankly, the best!
Free Lessons – The Generator, 3d, Quixel Mixer and Unreal Engine 4!
Making a Necron Monolith – for 3d Printing, Rendering or just whatever!
3d is Fundemental – Enough Basics to Start
CGPirates Wednesday Shorties! Making a purchased Character Work in UE4
Captain Blue’s Reviews : Game FPS Kit for UE4
CGPirates Longstream – Building The Framework For a Hidden Chapel
The Bothy
YARRR Timelapse?
YARRRR!!!
Making a Bothy.
Building a Bothy 1 – Creating The Prefabs in 3ds Max
Building a Bothy 2
Unwrapping in 3ds Max
Introducing Unreal Engine 4
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – A guide for students parents and carers
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – How it is installed, What is it for?
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – Making your first project in Unreal Engine 4
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – Moving objects around
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – Rotating, Scaling and Fine Tuning
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – Deleting and Adding Things to your Level
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – Shadows and light builds
Introducing Unreal Engine 4 – Making a VERY simple level!
Unreal Engine 4 : The Lighthouse Chapter Two
Unreal Engine 4 Lighthouse Downloading A Megascans Asset for the project
Unreal Engine 4 Lighthouse Importing the Megascans rock asset
Unreal Engine 4 Lighthouse Assembling Your Imported Rock Asset
Unreal Engine 4 Lighthouse Enabling Displacement in your Material
Unreal Engine 4 Basic Material Overview : The Normal Map
Unreal Engine 4 Basic Materials Overview : The Ambient Occlusion Map
Unreal Engine 4 Basic Material Overview : Housekeeping
Introduction to Blender
CGPirates Introduction to Blender : Downloading and Installing
CGPirates Introduction to Blender : Starting the App and Moving Around the Screen
CGPirates Introduction to Blender : Editing a Polygon Object
The Wickie
About CGPirates
Cookie policy (EU)
Patrons Only!
Cookie policy (EU)
This Cookie Policy was last updated on December 9, 2019 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.1. IntroductionOur website, https://cgpirates.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on “Save preferences”, you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.5.1 Manage your consent settings6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.6.3 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter and Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter and Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter and Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter and Instagram are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesJetPack
We use JetPack for advertizing.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
tk_ai
session
Store a unique user ID
Sharing
For more information, please read the JetPack Privacy Statement.
Visual Composer
We use Visual Composer for website design.
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
vchideactivationmsg_vc11
vc4-templates
vc4-templates_expiresIn
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Elementor
We use Elementor for content creation.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
elementor
persistent
Count and track pageviews
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
WooCommerce
We use WooCommerce for webshop management.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
wc_cart_hash_*
session
Store items in shopping cart
wc_fragments_*
persistent
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Vimeo
We use Vimeo for video display.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
__utmt_player
2 years
Track audience reach
Statistics
vuid
2 years
Store the user’s usage history
Sharing
For more information, please read the Vimeo Privacy Statement.
YouTube
We use YouTube for video display.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
PREF
1 year
Track visits across websites
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Statement.
Facebook
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
actppresence
1 year
Manage ad display frequency
fbm_
Sharing
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.
Twitter
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
metrics_token
persistent
Stores if the user has seen embedded content
Sharing
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Statement.
Miscellaneous
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
uber_menu_settings_tab
csUIPreferences
complianz_consent_status
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Captain Blue
1006 Henley Gardens
Durham
United Kingdom
Website: https://cgpirates.com
Email: cris@cgpirates.com
Phone number: 01207592020This Cookie Policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on December 9, 2019
YARR Matey! Come chat!
How is your week?
